<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home</title>
    <link>https://benschau.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 15:38:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://benschau.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Homelab Beginnings</title>
      <link>https://benschau.com/posts/homelab-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 16:33:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benschau.com/posts/homelab-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>Recently, after having graduated from college, I figured I wanted to spend some of the cash I saved up during college to finally kickstart a real homelab. A couple goals to keep in mind:
 Wanted to be able to run more intensive programs, distributed stuff (MPI, RPC) on &amp;lsquo;separate&amp;rsquo; machines.  Virtual clusters for the distributed stuff, and compiling bigger projects would ease my pain for things like contributing to big open source projects (Linux kernel, Firefox, which I wanted to do but haven&amp;rsquo;t had the heart to try and get into).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Wake Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://benschau.com/posts/alan-wake-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 19:34:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benschau.com/posts/alan-wake-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Since I&amp;rsquo;ve graduated, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally got some time to finish some of the games I bought a while ago. I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be interesting to talk about how I felt about some of those games I finished in a &amp;lsquo;review&amp;rsquo; of sorts. For the most part, this retrospective does have some spoilers, since the most intriguing part of the game is the plot.
To start things off, I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing a classic from the 2010s, Alan Wake, made by Remedy Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://benschau.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 15:38:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benschau.com/about/</guid>
      <description>A blog that I occasionally update; just for me to write about things that I find interesting. Hopefully it serves as a motivator for me to keep up with tech stuff, but also with a bunch of miscellaneous topics as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The_non_first_post</title>
      <link>https://benschau.com/posts/the_non_first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 15:19:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benschau.com/posts/the_non_first_post/</guid>
      <description>This is a reboot of the blog that I had earlier at this domain; a couple years ago, I started getting pretty bogged down by college and stopped posting to keep focused. I&amp;rsquo;ve since graduated at this point, so I figured I would wipe my blog clean and do it over. So, this is that post. Switched up the theme as well, this is much more clean.
Maybe at some point, I&amp;rsquo;ll even try to self-host this site instead of running it off Github and using a different domain name for it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>